Donovan Desmond is a dangerous man
who threatens the peace between
the East and the West.
To get close to him,
we succeeded in enrolling Anya
at the Eden Academy,
where his son attends.
In order to access the reception
that Desmond will attend,
Anya needs to become an honors student,
by earning eight Stella Medals,
which are given to outstanding students.
But that's not easy to accomplish
at the elite school.
So I devised a Plan B,
the "Friendship Strategy."
I had hoped for her to build
a friendship with Desmond's son, Damian,
and maybe even have us parents
befriend each other.
But on the first day of school,
she punched him,
and ended up with one Tonito
and a bad relationship with him…
No, it's too early to give up.
The plan has only begun.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION:7 TARGET: THE SECOND SON
Good morning.
Good morning, Yor. Breakfast is ready.
The three of us have grown accustomed
to our life together.
Is Anya still sleeping?
Does she feel bad about yesterday?
I'm not mad, so come out.
You'll be late if you don't hurry and eat.
Anya's sorry she sucks at school.
No, it's my fault…
Don't worry about the past.
Just be careful not to get into
any more fights in the future.
Come on, cheer up! Classes start today.
You're so kind, Loid!
It's more constructive
to use my thoughts on future measures
than to drag out a mistake.
Besides, I'll be in more trouble
if she starts saying
that she doesn't want to go to school.
For the sake of the mission,
we must make sure that her school life
is smooth sailing at all costs.
Oh, also, make sure you
apologize to Damian at school.
Understand?
Yes. I'll be off.
Be a good girl and do your best!
We need to head to work too.
I'm counting on you, Anya.
World peace depends on
how you make up with him.
Anya will do her best!
Have a good day, Lady Becky.
Lady!
Hello, Anya!
Lady! Do you live in a castle?
Of course not!
Did you come on the school bus?
I can give you a ride in my car next time.
Can Anya become a Lady too?
Nobody said anything about adopting you.
Boarding students are lucky
they don't have to commute!
Ew.
What do you mean "Ew"? How rude!
You're so annoying, even in the morning!
-What did you say?!
-How arrogant!
Bleh!
Make sure you apologize.
Um… About yesterday…
Let's go, Anya. Class is going to start!
Hey, wait!
Talking to those people
will only make us stupid too.
But, world peace!
HE WAS WORRIED,
SO HE ENDED UP FOLLOWING HER
Don't bother her, Blackbell girl!
But wait… Blackbell and the Desmond group
are business partners…
Is that girl interfering with
our operations at the behest of
an enemy organization?
No, wait. That can't be.
The first few days of school are
crucial in creating a group of friends.
We must reconcile them
by the end of the day!
Well, this is…
That's the girl who was violent, right?
How scary!
Is her friend a delinquent too?
She punched him for no reason, right?
How awful!
Why do I have to be
in the same class as her?
What if she punches me too?
How can she come to school?
What a nuisance!
School is so scary…
People are so shallow.
They can only see what's visible
on the surface.
Are you a smart person?
Not really!
By the way, call me Becky!
Get to your seats!
I hope we can become better friends!
I'm the only one who knows
the positive things about Anya!
People like them are seriously…
If we get too close…
School is scary, but I think I'll be okay.
Isn't this cute?
Ugh!
Why won't you say anything, Mr. Damian?
-That's right. My name is Damian Desmond.
-I'll take roll call!
I'm the second son of a prominent family
and was raised in the lap of luxury.
No one has ever defied me.
-Even my brother had never struck me, but…
-Oh, he's the Chairman's son.
Damian!
-But…!
-Damian!
Here.
I've never felt this way before…
This way…
This way…!
-Johnny.
-Here.
-Jesse.
-Carl.
-Here.
Today is your first day of class,
so before we begin, I'd like to start…
The starting line for all of you
who passed through
the difficult exams to enter our school…
When the relationship between
this and this is like this…
…which is why this becomes like this
and this becomes this.
That's why this answer is like this and…
If you understand this, you can
do the same thing to get the answer here.
Sleeping during the first day of school…
She must be a delinquent after all…
How scary.
Anya! Next is science class!
-Wake up!
-The second son!
Anya has to apologize to the second son!
The second son? Damian already left.
It's fine! Don't bother with him!
If I don't apologize to the second son,
the peace will be disturbed!
You mean peaceful school life
will be disrupted?
I guess you're right.
We don't know what he'll do.
But don't worry! I'm on your side!
I'll protect you, no matter what happens!
-I guess it's okay then.
-Yeah!
No, it's not okay!
Huh? Father!
I need to somehow show her
that an apology is necessary!
Thus sunlight can be reflected by mirrors.
There is heat in the area where
light is reflected.
FORTUNE TELLING FOR GOOD CHILDREN
IT IS GOOD TO APOLOGIZE TODAY
Is this from God?
We'll use another mirror
to reflect the light.
Apologize Anya. Make up with him.
I feel so much pressure!
Then John made up his mind.
Even if it meant being ostracized,
he said he would stand up for his beliefs.
John never apologized
to anyone after that.
Why is my textbook different?
BUT JOHN RECALLED…
THAT SOMETIMES IT'S IMPORTANT TO APOLOGIZE
AND GET ALONG WITH OTHERS.
LUNCH BREAK
It's finally lunchtime!
Let's go to the dining room!
This is a prestigious school indeed.
The classes are relentless from day one!
I'm exhausted!
New students!
You may order anything you like
from the menu!
I'm sure he won't compare to
our chef at home.
Anya wants an omelet with rice!
That's a strange dish.
Oh, the second son!
Ugh! Why doesn't he eat at the dorm!
-I have to apologize!
-It's fine!
They're the ones who were mean!
That kid!
Darn it. I have to get her away from Anya!
Hey newbie! Where are you going?
First year, class three.
-Becky Blackbell, come to Building A.
-What?
-The student hall.
-But I'm eating lunch!
It's urgent!
Ugh, fine!
It's my chance to apologize!
Are you going to come at us again?!
Um…
Mr. Damian won't lose against you
unless you take him by surprise!
Um!
Shut up, you guys.
-Wha--?
-Are you going to take her on by yourself?
Why is it that I'm at a loss for words
whenever she's in front of me?
Mr. Damian?
What is this feeling in my heart?
I feel chills… I'll quickly apologize
and run away.
Knowing him,
he must be pondering over awful words
that will shred her heart into pieces!
What kind of shot will he take? "Runt"?
No, it has to be something
more awful than that!
-U-Um…
-Ugly? Raccoon face?
-Violent gorilla girl?
-Anya…
What's with that ugly,
horn-like hair accessory!
-Yesterday…
-Your mom must be an outie!
Short legs!
What's with that ugly,
horn-like hair accessory!
A commoner that looks like a raccoon!
Get out of here before you spread
your commoner germs, you raccoon!
Short legs like a raccoon!
I'm sorry for suddenly
punching you yesterday!
Anya actually wants to
be friends with you!
I'm sorry! Anya has short legs…
-She feels so guilty that she's sobbing?!
-I'm sorry…
What a sweet girl!
I guess I didn't need to prompt her.
Good girl, Anya. You did well.
Mr. Damian, your face is red.
This is… from anger! How can I…?
That's right. She directly defied me!
Right. Directly. In front of my face!
Staring directly at me!
No. It's not like that! Stop thumping!
A person like me towards
a commoner like her?
No way. That's so embarrassing!
Screw you! I won't accept that
even if I die!
I won't accept it!
My pride will never accept it!
Wow! Mr. Damian didn't even
bat an eye to a girl's tears!
We'll let you off easy today!
Mr. Damian!
He completely rejected her apology?!
Plan B is dead!
Wait, why are you running away?
Shut up!
School is scary…
RELATIONSHIP WITH DAMIAN: ?
Becky…!
Who was it?!
Who called me out here!
BUILDING A - STUDENT HALL
That's a third
with a denominator of three.
So three thirds, make one whole.
It's easy, right?
Loid. Shall we take a little break?
No. She needs to memorize this today.
The recent incident with Damian…
The Friendship Strategy,
-to befriend the Desmond Family…
-I won't accept it!
…has been completely destroyed.
Now, we must go with Plan A
and improve our chances of
becoming an honors student
as much as possible…
If you don't finish this, you can't watch
your spy cartoon this afternoon.
Come on. What's the answer for this one?
I'll read Father's mind
and finish quickly!
You use this formula for this…
One can earn stars
through sports and social contributions
in addition to academics in order to
advance as an honors student,
but the first step is to improve academic
performance and achieve stable results
in order to prevent the accumulation of
Tonitos due to poor performance…
Are you all right, Anya?
I'll read Mother's mind!
Mother, this problem!
Let's do it together!
So the denominator is five,
so split one into five…
So to explain it simply,
separate the limbs from the body…
Oh, but the head will be in the way…
Huh? So, five…
Five is similar to S.
Are you all right, Anya?
What's wrong? Why can't you solve it?
To be honest, I don't understand
what she doesn't understand.
I don't want to study!
Hey! Wait!
L… Loid!
Maybe it's not good to force her…
But she has to study more
in order to become an honors student.
Is that what she wants too?
That's…
For the sake of my mission.
I want Anya to enjoy going to school.
Of course, she'll also need to study
so she won't get expelled.
You're… right.
She's probably too young
to care about grades.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to overstep
the boundaries of your household.
No, it's fine. Thank you, Yor.
I can't help but lose my cool
when dealing with her.
I'm sure other parents are the same way.
Let's take a break. I'll pour some tea.
Anya! There's hot cocoa!
ANYA
She's not coming out…
She's sulking.
Anya will do her best in school!
She reminds me of my brother
when he was young.
She'll eventually come out.
By the way, your brother works for
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, right?
He must have had good grades.
Did you oversee his studies?
If you have any tips on how to teach…
No, Yuri was much smarter than I was.
So it's embarrassing to admit,
but he actually taught me a lot of things.
Whenever we studied together, he always…
No, Sis!
Spiders aren't insects!
Insects are those with
six legs, and a separate
head, chest, and body!
Really? You're so knowledgeable, Yuri!
Every time I praised him,
he'd break into a huge smile.
-Sis, I'll teach you history next!
-Okay!
He must've had fun teaching me because
he always studied without being told.
Wake up, Sis! I memorized
my times tables! Listen!
Yeah…
I see.
He was motivated by
his sister's recognition.
I'm not sure about that, but…
if that was the case,
maybe you can become
a person like that for Anya.
It might be a good idea to
praise any effort she makes,
no matter how small it may be.
I think that'll make Anya happy.
Maybe…
At the end of the day,
I'm not her real parent.
No, I'm wrong.
I should've
been an ideal father to her first.
I should've acted that way.
That should've been the base
of this mission. But what did I do?
I've been far from the ideal father.
As a father, I'm…
Don't worry.
Have confidence in yourself.
Remember how Anya gave you a score
of 100%?
Anya considers you a great father!
I really appreciate that.
I didn't mean to overstep again!
I'm a stranger, after all.
No, Yor.
You're no stranger.
You're the mother of the Forger household.
I rely on you for things that are
beyond my capability.
Th… That's right.
I was a wife.
Be careful not to forget
when you're out and about.
If you'd like, please oversee
Anya's studies.
Sure, if it's fine with you.
Let's not rush and work together!
That's right. Don't rush, Twilight.
There are many ways to simply
assassinate Desmond
and get away with it,
but that will not solve the real problem.
Nothing can be done overnight.
We have to gain their trust
and get into their minds
and observe what they are thinking
and what they want.
Only by performing this tedious
and patient duty can you become a spy!
First, I must understand Anya.
Oh, look at the time!
I'm going to go have a chat with Anya.
Okay, I'll go do some dishes then.
Hey, Anya!
Your spy cartoon is going to start!
I'm sorry about earlier.
We can go through your work again
once you watch your cartoon.
Anya?
She fell asleep…
You're going to catch a cold.
Was she studying by herself?
For Father…
I have to get the highest grade…
I guess I'll record the cartoon for her.
Mother, you can't kill father…
What kind of dream is she having?
A great father, huh?
I wonder what it'd feel like
to have a real family.
Hey, Yuri!
Long time no see, Dominic!
I've been so busy with work
that I haven't been home at all!
After all you're the elite for
the Foreign Ministry!
By the way, Dominic,
how was the party the other day?
-What kind of man was my sister with?
-Yor's?
Oh actually, congratulations!
Wait, you haven't met him yet?
Huh?
Sis was married?
MISSION:8
THE COUNTER-SECRET POLICE COVER OPERATION
Subtitle translations by: Nana Onishi